Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures Documenting Basketball
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Men's basketball game videotapes, 1991-2007; Accession 2016-A-019
  - Yale vs. Cornell, February 7, 2004; 1 (Box 66)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 13, 2004; 1 (Box 67)
  - Harvard vs. Yale, February 14, 2004; 1 (Box 68)
  - Princeton vs. Yale, February 20, 2004; 1 (Box 69)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, February 21, 2004; 1 (Box 70)
  - Yale vs. Harvard, February 27, 2004; 1 (Box 71)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 28, 2004 (Box 72)
  - Cornell vs. Yale, March 5, 2004; 1 (Box 73)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, March 6, 2004; 1 (Box 74)
  - Wagner scrimmage, November 7, 2004; 1 (Box 75)
  - Radford vs. Yale, November 19, 2004; 1 (Box 76)
  - Hartford vs. Yale/William and Mary vs. Yale, November 20, 2004; 1 (Box 77)
  - Yale vs. Wake Forest, November 22, 2004; 1 (Box 78)
  - Yale vs. University of Massachusetts, November 28, 2004; 1 (Box 79)
  - Yale vs. Sacred Heart, December 1, 2004; 1 (Box 80)
  - Bucknell vs. Yale, December 4, 2004; 1 (Box 81)
  - Yale vs. Niagara, December 8, 2004; 1 (Box 82)
  - "Tourney Hoops", December 12, 2004; 1 (Box 83)
  - Yale vs. Boston College, December 19, 2004; 1 (Box 84)
  - University of North Carolina-Charlotte vs. Yale (Cable Car Classic in Santa Clara, CA), December 28, 2004; 1 (Box 85)
  - Yale vs. Santa Clara, December 29, 2004; 1 (Box 86)
  - Yale Highlights, 2004-2005; 1 (Box 87)
  - Fairfield vs. Yale, January 5, 2005; 1 (Box 88)
  - American vs. Yale, January 10, 2005; 1 (Box 89)
  - St. Peter's vs. Yale, January 15, 2005; 1 (Box 90)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, January 29, 2005; 1 (Box 91)
  - Yale vs. Pennsylvania, January 29, 2005; 1 (Box 92)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, February 4, 2005; 1 (Box 93)
  - Cornell vs. Yale, February 5, 2005; 1 (Box 94)
  - Bill Walsh-Yale University, February 12, 2005; 1 (Box 95)
  - Harvard vs. Yale, February 12, 2005; 1 (Box 96)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, February 18, 2005; 1 (Box 97)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, February 19, 2005; 1 (Box 98)
  - Brown vs. Yale, February 22, 2005; 1 (Box 99)
  - Harvard vs. Yale, February 25, 2005; 1 (Box 100)
  - Yale vs. Dartmouth, February 26, 2005; 1 (Box 101)
  - Yale vs. Cornell, March 4, 2005; 1 (Box 102)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, March 5, 2005; 1 (Box 103)
  - Yale vs. Brown, March 8, 2005 (Box 104)
  - Stony Brook vs. Yale, November 9, 2005; 1 (Box 105)
  - Yale vs. Louisiana Tech (at Lincoln, Nebraska), November 18, 2005; 1 (Box 106)
  - Yale vs. Nebraska (John Thompson Classic), November 19, 2005; 1 (Box 107)
  - Longwood vs. Yale (at Lincoln, Nebraska), November 20, 2005; 1 (Box 108)
  - Yale vs. Bucknell, November 26, 2005; 1 (Box 109)
  - Sacred Heart vs. Yale, November 28, 2005
    - Master, 1 (Box 110)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 110U)
  - Wagner vs. Yale, December 3, 2005; 1 (Box 111)
  - Yale vs. Hartford, December 8, 2005; 1 (Box 112)
  - Yale vs. Hampton, December 18, 2005
    - Master, 1 (Box 113)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 113U)
  - Navy vs. Yale, December 20, 2005; 1 (Box 114)
  - Navy. vs. Yale, December 22, 2005; 1 (Box 115)
  - Yale vs. Providence, December 22, 2005
    - Master, 1 (Box 116)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 116U)
  - James Madison vs. Yale, December 29, 2005; 1 (Box 117)
  - Savannah State vs. Yale, December 30, 2005; 1 (Box 118)
  - Blue-White scrimmage, 2005-2006; 1 (Box 119)
  - Yale vs. Rice, January 2, 2006
    - Master, 1 (Box 120)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 120U)
  - Yale vs. American, January 9, 2006; 1 (Box 121)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 14, 2006; 1 (Box 122)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 21, 2006; 1 (Box 123)
  - Harvard vs. Yale, January 27, 2006; 1 (Box 124)
  - Yale vs. Princeton, February 3, 2006; 1 (Box 125)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, February 4, 2006; 1 (Box 126)
  - Columbia vs. Yale, February 10, 2006
    - Master, 1 (Box 127)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 127U)
  - Cornell vs. Yale, February 11, 2006; 1 (Box 128)
  - Yale vs. Columbia, February 25, 2006; 1 (Box 129)
  - Pennsylvania vs. Yale, March 3, 2006; 1 (Box 130)
  - Princeton vs. Yale, March 4, 2006; 1 (Box 131)
  - Yale vs. Sacred Heart, December 4, 2006; 1 (Box 132)
  - Yale vs. Brown, January 13, 2007; 1 (Box 133)
  - Undated recordings
    - Cason, Alex, Sam, Ed, 1 (Box 134)
    - Dominick Martin edit tape, 1 (Box 135)
    - Italy #2, 1 (Box 136)
    - URI vs. Yale, 1 (Box 137)
    - Yale vs. Army, 1 (Box 138)
    - Yale vs. Coastal, 1 (Box 139)
    - Yale vs. Columbia, 1 (Box 140)
    - Yale vs. Columbia, 1 (Box 141)
    - Yale vs. Eastern Michigan, 1 (Box 142)
    - Yale vs. Harvard, 1 (Box 143)
    - Yale vs. Princeton, 1 (Box 144)
    - Yale vs. URI, 1 (Box 145)
    - Yale vs. Wake Forest, 1 (Box 146)